Their laws. His rules.
Rebel Ridge is a crime, action, thriller film directed by Jeremy Saulnier.
A former Marine confronts corruption in a small town when local law enforcement
unjustly seizes the bag of cash he needs to post his cousin's bail.
Terry Richmond, played by Aaron Pierre.
Chief Sandy Burnne, played by Don Johnson.
Summer McBride, played by AnnaSophia Robb.
Officer Steve Lann, played by Emory Cohen.
Officer Evan Marston, played by David Denman.
Skinny Guard, played by Oscar Gale.
Rebel Ridge is a 2024 American action thriller film written,
produced, directed and edited by Jeremy Saulnier.
The film stars Aaron Pierre as Terry Richmond, a former Marine; he has the funds needed to post bail for his
cousin, but the money is unjustly seized via civil forfeiture by a small town's corrupt police force.
Don Johnson, AnnaSophia Robb, David Denman, Emory Cohen, Steve Zissis, Zsané
Jhé, Dana  Lee, and James Cromwell also appear in the film.
Rebel Ridge was released by Netflix on September 6,
2024 to positive critical reviews.
It won the Critics' Choice Television Award for Best Movie Made for Television
and the Primetime Emmy Award for Outstanding Television Movie.
The film explores themes of small town,
corruption, police chief, louisiana, money.
The tone is intense.